<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Week 4s on TEAM EAT</title>
    <link>/week-4/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Week 4s on TEAM EAT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/week-4/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/week-4/week4-enaceanu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/week-4/week4-enaceanu/</guid>
      <description>Alex’s Blog Week 3 Continuation of Project 1 There was still a lot of work to do with Terraform and Ansible, plus of course the many issues that arose. We got a new addition to the team and decided to delegate Ansible tasks to him. Luckily, last week I learned a lot about Terraform by writing and testing code for the NAT/Bastion and blog server instances. I also reviewed a lot of different example code, from Terraforms website which is very helpful especially with regards to modifying code with arguments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/week-4/week4-sandoval/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/week-4/week4-sandoval/</guid>
      <description>Week 4 Blog The rundown this Week Tasks completed This week I ran into a bit of issues in configuring the s3 bucket initially I had setup my terraform code in the correct format. The first part of my issue is that I did not realize that I needed a back end snippet that would allow me to sync up the current .tfstate file. I needed to include a back end portion which would remotely sync the .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/week-4/week4-blomquist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/week-4/week4-blomquist/</guid>
      <description>Erik&amp;rsquo;s Blog. Week 4 What&amp;rsquo;s new this week? Project 1 This week has been all about finishing up the Terraform tasks and for it to work with Ansible. One problem I ran into this week was that I could not SSH into our instances using my Mac. It gave me the error &amp;ldquo;Permission denied (publickey)&amp;rdquo; many times over, here is how I solved it.
How to connect to AWS instances using SSH (Mac &amp;amp; Linux users) Setup and configure AWS Command Line Interface (CLI)  Open your terminal and run &amp;ldquo;pip install awscli&amp;rdquo; and wait for it to install.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/week-4/week4-karim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/week-4/week4-karim/</guid>
      <description>Shahid&amp;rsquo;s Blog. Week 4 What&amp;rsquo;s new this week? Learning about Ansible Much like a bash script allows a user to run several commands at once, Ansible allows an administrator to apply several changes to a server or group of servers at once. This is done with a list of commands that&amp;rsquo;s consolidated into a yml file called a playbook.
Bash Script vs Ansible Playbook Here is a simple bash script: apt-get install apache2 apt-get install git  Wow the Bash Script looks really short right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/week-4/week4-kluszczynski/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/week-4/week4-kluszczynski/</guid>
      <description>Tyler&amp;rsquo;s Blog. Week 4 What&amp;rsquo;s new this week? Finishing Project 1 Although Project 1 was much more organized than Project 0, we still have some work to do in terms of organization. This will be discussed during the presentation this coming Monday.
One of my tasks for this project was setting up the certificate for our web servers. Instead of doing this through certbot like in project 0, I used AWS Certificate Manager.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>